His family thinks he's crazy. His enemies think he's no
challenge. But she knows he's THE LAST DRAGON.
The Last Dragon is a action, adventure, music film directed by Michael Schultz.
A young man searches for the "master" to obtain the final
level of martial arts mastery known as the glow.
Along the way he must fight an evil martial arts expert and rescue a
beautiful singer from an obsessed music promoter.
Leroy Green, played by Taimak.
Laura Charles, played by Vanity.
Eddie Arkadian, played by Christopher Murney.
Sho'nuff / The Shogun of Harlem, played by Julius Carry.
Angela Viracco, played by Faith Prince.
Richie Green, played by Leo O'Brien.
The Last Dragon (sometimes listed as Berry Gordy's The Last Dragon) is a 1985 American musical martial arts film
directed by Michael Schultz, written by Louis Venosta, and produced by Rupert Hitzig for Berry Gordy.
The film stars Taimak, Vanity, Julius Carry, Christopher
Murney, Keshia Knight Pulliam and Faith Prince.
Choreography was created by Lester Wilson and Lawrence Leritz.
The Last Dragon was released in theaters by Tri-Star Pictures on March 22, 1985.
The film was a financial success despite a mixed reception by critics and is
considered a cult classic, especially in urban Black cinema.
The film explores themes of martial arts, kung fu,
kidnapping, pop singer, pizzeria.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.